[{"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Christopher Walken plays a powerful drug lord alongside Laurence Fishburne in this 1990 feature film, directed by Abel Ferrara.", "correct_answer": "King of New York", "incorrect_answers": ["Cat Chaser", "Dangerous Game", "Biloxi Blues"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the name of the capital and largest city of Spain?", "correct_answer": "Madrid", "incorrect_answers": ["Rome", "Milan", "Valencia"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jaguars closely resemble which other big cats in physical appearance?", "correct_answer": "Leopard", "incorrect_answers": ["Tiger", "Cheetah", "Puma"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "Jane Marple, better known as Miss Marple, is a fictional amateur detective created by this famous author.", "correct_answer": "Agatha Christie", "incorrect_answers": ["Arthur Conan Doyle", "Edgar Allan Poe", "Raymond Chandler"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This group, formed in the late 1930s, are known for the song If I Didnt Care.", "correct_answer": "The Ink Spots", "incorrect_answers": ["The Ink Boys", "The Ink Sounds", "The Ink Brothers"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "This 2000 film is a fictionalized account of the making of 1922s Nosferutu.", "correct_answer": "Shadow of the Vampire", "incorrect_answers": ["Embrace of the Vampire", "The Forsaken", "Moon Child"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What are the largest cities in the Philippines in terms of land area?", "correct_answer": "Davao City and Puerto Princesa City", "incorrect_answers": ["Manila and Davao City", "Zamballes and Puerto Princesa City", "Zamballes and Manila"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What is the meaning of the name of Spain according to a popular theory?", "correct_answer": "All of these", "incorrect_answers": ["Land of rabbits", "Edge", "Land of the setting sun"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "In 1994, the T-Rex in Jurassic Park won the Best Villain award in what movie awards program?", "correct_answer": "MTV Movie Awards", "incorrect_answers": ["The Peoples Choice Awards", "The Academy Awards", "The Academy of Science Fiction, Fantasy and Horror Films"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What actress won the Academy Award for Best Actress for the portrayal of Loretta Castorini in the romantic comedy Moonstruck?", "correct_answer": "Cher", "incorrect_answers": ["Olympia Dukakis", "Sophia Loren", "Meryl Streep"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "The movie The Breakfast Club was rated PG-13.", "correct_answer": "False", "incorrect_answers": ["True"]}, {"type": "multiple", "difficulty": "unknown", "category": "General", "question": "What happens to the Donkey in the 2004 movie Shrek 2, one of the highest-grossing films in history?", "correct_answer": "He becomes a father.", "incorrect_answers": ["He is kidnapped.", "He falls in love with a mare.", "All of these"]}]